// Questions Array
var questions = [
    {
        question: "Question 1",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1" // change to string
    },
    {
        question: "Question 2",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 3",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 4",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 5",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer:"Answer 1"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 6",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 7",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 8",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 9",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 10",
        answers: ["Answer 1", "Answer 2", "Answer 3", "Answer 4"],
        answer: "Answer 1"
    }




];
